{
    "id": "b0f1b539b64b49d1a262113f224bb6ae",
    "title": "Third conditional grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "0277d72c3f40474e8f6a472eb1cb7aeb",
            "title": "Third Conditional Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "If I had known her name, I ………………………… you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will tell",
                        "would tell",
                        "would have told"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you ……………………….. me, I would have told you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ask",
                        "asked",
                        "had asked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you hadn’t helped me, I …………………………… in real trouble.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will be",
                        "would be",
                        "would have been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He would have died if they ……………………………. him to hospital in time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "didn't take",
                        "don't take",
                        "hadn't taken"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Jane ……………………. if you had invited her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will come",
                        "would come",
                        "would have come"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He would have helped you if you ………………………… more politely.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "request",
                        "requested",
                        "had requested"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I had wanted to, I ………………………. anybody I like.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can marry",
                        "could marry",
                        "could have married"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If he had run a bit faster, he …………………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can win",
                        "could win",
                        "could have won"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If my grandmother ………………………….. alive, she would have been 85 now.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "had been",
                        "has been",
                        "is"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you ………………………… harder, you would have passed your exam.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "work",
                        "worked",
                        "had worked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}